Jax. JAX. Look at me. Three
world leaders said "months."
MONTHS.
RAVEN
All of them! The ones with the
hats AND the ones without hats!
RAVEN
I literally told you this would
happen. I have a 47-page
document. I LAMINATED it.
RAVEN
I laminated a SURVIVAL PLAN. We
need 400 cans of beans, a hand-
crank radio, and I'm pricing out
bunkers on Craigslist —
RAVEN
Gary in Ohio has one. Reasonable
square footage.
RAVEN
...Nothing yet.
What.
RAVEN
There are no coincidences, Jax.
The timing —
RAVEN
...I hate that that's almost
logical.
RAVEN
Wait — which world leaders?
JAX
Okay but is that bad?
You laminated a war.
JAX
There are bunkers on Craigslist?
What'd you get me for the
apocalypse?
JAX
I got myself something.
New game. Seventy hours of
content. If WW3 starts I'll deal
with it after I finish the
tutorial.
JAX
Babe. If the world ends, you're
gonna want someone who's
relaxed.
JAX
That's wild. You want another
beer?
JAX